I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
We ended up at an old house
with a fishing hole.
He's vicious! Watch out!
C'mere!
I used to have a dog.
You're amazing, Izumi-chan.
Hmm...
First, you let him sniff your fist.
And when the dog knows your scent,
you stroke it very gently.
You see?
'Kay.
First, you let him sniff your fist...
and then stroke his head...
Beck! Stop it!
Yo!
Beck, go play by yourself.
Ryusuke-kun!
Is this your house, Ryusuke-kun?
Yup. As well as my workplace.
It has character.
Sorry, my house is old.
Well...you can use it however you like.
All right.
-See you tomorrow.
-Bye-bye, Grandma. See ya.
This place is really comfortable.
You have so many CDs.
-And...
-Lots of girls' romances, right?
My kid sister left 'em,
and I got hooked on them.
Young girls' comics?
This one's good.
Christy Sakuishi's "Happy Sangokushi".
Oh, I know that one!
Look! Wow!
This is a Dying Breed CD
from their indie days!
Huh? Oh yeah...
This one's worth a lot now.
Oh yeah?
That cover's from the band, Australia.
Wow! I'd love to hear it!
The original one was quite country.
Kinda like "Drag Car Boy."
Oh, I have "Drag Car Boy."
Eddie's totally into it.
I can't follow their conversation at all.
-You than before
Close your eyes, no need to panic
Feel the void, feel the beat,
there's no need to say it
-Tomorrow will surely be wow wow
-Yukio! Telephone!
-So cheer up,
because I want to see your smile
-Someone named Minami-san.
-So cheer up,
because I want to see your smile
-Minami? A man?
Hello?
Oh, Ryusuke-kun!
Yeah. Live on Sunday, right?
Yup. I'll tell Izumi-chan too.
Uh-huh...Yup.
I also wanna tell you something.
Huh? What is it?
You're 14. And I'm 16 years old.
So just call me "Ryusuke".
When a guy calls me "Ryusuke-kun",
it feels creepy.
You listening?
You think it's funny?
So it's the Japanese way...
what society expects.
But are you listening?
I'm just not into
feudalistic practices like that.
Koyuki, did you hear me?
Okay. I'll call you
just Ryusuke from now on.
I'll see you on Sunday.
Sorry I'm late!
Koyuki-san! What were you
doing at the intersection?
Did you lose something?
C'mon, let's go.
Ryusuke-kun drew me
this map to the live house.
-All simple hiragana.
-I guess he can't write kanji.
Say, Izumi-chan.
Hmm? What is it?
Why don't you start seeing Ryusuke-kun?
I mean, he's cool...
Oh, right! I want you to
listen to something, Koyuki!
Here it is.
This.
This is Dying Breed.
What's the matter?
This is...
Oh, sorry! The battery's dead!
Izumi-chan!
Oh, Kayo-chan! You're late!
Sorry, sorry!
Dying...Breed.
Koyuki, hurry it up!
We'll leave you behind!
This way.
Hey!
This is...an interesting place.
-Oh, there's a good crowd.
-Yeah.
These are tonight's bands.
What's wrong, Koyuki?
A live house...
Wait! That's-!
Cut the crap!
Can't you listen to me?!
The entire band agreed to it.
I like my black hair.
Hey, thanks for coming.
Err...Umm...
Ryusuke...
If you expect to be a pro,
you'd better listen to me.
That white outfit
the other time was the pits.
-Stop it!
-That's enough!
There's a scout in the audience tonight!
With any luck, we can quit our
part-time jobs and focus on our music!
-Understand?!
-Eiji!
-Leggo of me!
-Let's go.
-Yeah...
Stop it!
They were really going at it.
They're all serious about this.
So they get uptight.
It's 1500 yen, right?
-Plus 500 yen for drinks.
-Here you go.
-All we need is get into the night
-So this is a live concert...
-People need it
-Wow...
-get into the night
-Maho...Minami.
-Let it the funk
-Ain't a thing
-14 years old.
-All we need is
-My kid sister.
-Get into the night
Let it the funk
We got to move in the world destruction
-Get in tha funky punky!
-Yeah!
Serial Mama.
Is that the name of Ryusuke-kun's band?
Yeah. Eiji-kun probably picked the name.
Serial Mama...
A year ago, Eiji-kun said he was
gonna make the ultimate band.
-The "ultimate band"?
Apparently, he really bugged
Ryusuke-kun about joining.
Say Kayo-chan...Is that him?
Oh yeah, from the production company.
Eiji-kun's friend brought him.
If things go well, a major debut
may no longer be just a dream.
-What do you think?
-Looks good.
I wonder if those two are okay.
I know! It's like they have two leaders,
and it's nerve-wracking just watching them.
Don't worry about 'em.
Two opposites with perfect techniques
combine to create that sound!
Those two lead guitars...
Man, talk about music!
Serial Mama...They are the best!
Oh, they're up.
Let's go up closer!
Yay!
Eiji! I love you!
Yahoo!
We're the Serial Mama!
Hey! That's weird!
Sorry about that!
We'll get it fixed, just a sec!
Hmm...Let's use this time
for some chit-chat!
Eiji, can I tell them that?
Boy, that was a shock.
Does this happen often?
A guitar string will break sometimes.
But something this bad never happens.
What a day for it to happen...
Can you connect the guitar line to C1?
Got it!
My shield is fine.
Not mine. It's broken.
I'll switch it!
-How long's it gonna take?!
-Hurry it up!
I got it. The effecter volume was too low.
Eiji!
Yo! I'm okay on my side!
Thank you for your patience! Let's go!
You're the best!
Huh?
They're having a wrap party
at a pub up the street.
-Won't you join us, Koyuki?
-Yeah.
Hey, Izumi-chan, are your ears okay?
Oh, that's right. It was your
first time at a live concert.
Don't worry. Your hearing
will return in a bit.
I'm going to call home.
We'll go on ahead.
"Pub New Shinshu"
-Okay, three orders of chuhai.
-Hey, gimme some beef tongue.
"Pub New Shinshu"
Hey, Eiji-kun and Ryusuke haven't
exchanged a word since the fight.
Geez...This band is really in trouble.
What are you saying, girl?!
The Eiji and Ryusuke duo
will be together forever!
I'm going to the john.
This is the pits!
Say, this is the toilet, right?
Oh, you're Ryusuke-kun's younger sister.
-Is this the toilet?
-Yeah, I think so.
Thanks.
Oh, I see. Maho-chan,
you're not good with kanji either.
What?!
Who the fuck are you?!
Idiot.
Dammit!
-You wench!
-You got Serial Mama all wrong!
Where's the sake?! Bring the sake!
-Shut up!
-Screw you!
Pankration began in ancient Greece,
and in modern England, it became
popular as the Lancashire style
and was adapted into what
we know today as free-style wrestling.
And many wrestlers
have come up the ranks
after going through
the notorious Snake Pit.
And famous among them is Karl Gotch.
-Want to listen to this?
-Can I borrow it?
Of course!
Ryusuke-kun is really something.
Yeah.
I hope you find something
to get passionate about, too.
Yeah.
You can give it back anytime.
See you!
Thanks!
I think Ishiguro-sempai
may have a thing for you.
-I don't think so...
-Neither do I.
Say, Ishiguro. You've been
awfully cheerful lately.
You think so?
I'm suspicious!
It was a mistake. You and me joining up.
Yes?
No, it's all right.
Yes, I'll be right there!
Yes, thank you!
It's the weekend,
and I can't even take off!
Hard luck.
You wouldn't understand
what I have to go through.
Not you, a CEO's son.
Ryusuke...
I'm going to form the ultimate band.
So will I.
Ryusuke-kun...
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Lately, I'm really into the love game!
"Next Episode"
Just kidding.